You know, if we're being honest, some of y'all would curse out an ex from high school if you
saw them in the grocery store, but you want people to leave Kamala alone about a genocide.
Ain't this the internet that love to talk about accountability?
The unmitigated goal to come outside and peddle books after you actively propagated,
continue to spread lies that were debunked and said that were you to get elected, you would
continue to allow for a genocide to take place using the same taxpayers money who are donating
to your campaign to come outside and do a book tour when the genocide that you helped create
is still happening is wild.
This is she says, I wrapped up that unproductive meeting with Netanyahu in under an hour and
walked out to address the press.
I sincerely reaffirmed my commitment to Israel's right to defend itself.
I added that how Israel did that mattered.
Not if you don't want to condition aid.
It doesn't matter what you think about how Israel should be defending itself if you're
not willing to push the levers of power to make it defend itself in a way that you find
morally permissible.
And you did not do that.
And there's so far in 177 pages has been no admission that you should have done that.
And by the way, all the support she gives to Israel also puts the Congo in danger.
I hope she don't never know a day at peace.
You damn rude, eh?